Unsupported software matters because healthcare applications often handle ePHI,
user identity, clinical workflows, patient portals, APIs, and integrations.
Teams should look for this issue in user-facing features, administrative tools,
background jobs, and service-to-service communication.
Dependency risks matters because healthcare applications often handle ePHI, user identity,
clinical workflows, patient portals, APIs, and integrations.
Teams should look for this issue in user-facing features, administrative tools,
background jobs, and service-to-service communication.
Vulnerable third-party libraries matters because healthcare applications often handle
ePHI, user identity, clinical workflows, patient portals, APIs, and integrations.
Teams should look for this issue in user-facing features, administrative tools,
background jobs, and service-to-service communication.
Supply chain concerns matters because healthcare applications often handle ePHI,
user identity, clinical workflows, patient portals, APIs, and integrations.
Teams should look for this issue in user-facing features, administrative tools,
background jobs, and service-to-service communication.
Patch management Dependency scanning Software inventory management Selected HIPAA mappings
for this topic include Section 164.308(a)(1)(ii)(B) - Risk management;
Section 164.308(a)(8) - Evaluation;
Section 164.308(a)(5)(ii)(B) - Protection from malicious software.